function initializeQuestions() {
    questionsDatabase = {
        'A': [
            { "question": "U.S. state where the Ozarks are located", "correctAnswers": ["Arkansas"] },
            { "question": "Country with the Saharan oasis city of Tamanrasset", "correctAnswers": ["Algeria"] },
            { "question": "Capital known as the White Marble City", "correctAnswers": ["Ashgabat"] },
            { "question": "European country home to Innsbruck", "correctAnswers": ["Austria"] },
            { "question": "Largest state in Brazil", "correctAnswers": ["Amazonas"] },
            { "question": "Capital of Turkiye", "correctAnswers": ["Ankara"] },
            { "question": "Dutch city known for its canals and Museum District", "correctAnswers": ["Amsterdam"] },
        ],
        'B': [
            { "question": "State in northeast Brazil", "correctAnswers": ["Bahia"] },
            { "question": "Country in southeast Asia known as the Land of the Thunder Dragon", "correctAnswers": ["Bhutan"] },
            { "question": "Body of water between India and Myanmar", "correctAnswers": ["Bay of Bengal", "Bengal Bay"] },
            { "question": "Large port city in South Korea's southeast", "correctAnswers": ["Busan"] },
            { "question": "Peninsula in northwest Mexico", "correctAnswers": ["Baja California", "Baja"] },
            { "question": "City and province in Catalonia", "correctAnswers": ["Barcelona"] },
            { "question": "Adriatic port city of over 300k", "correctAnswers": ["Bari"] },
        ],
        'C': [
            { "question": "Capital of Venezuela", "correctAnswers": ["Caracas"] },
            { "question": "Country home to Chengdu, Chongqing, and Changchun", "correctAnswers": ["China"] },
            { "question": "Japanese city and prefecture east of Tokyo", "correctAnswers": ["Chiba"] },
            { "question": "Massive geological region encircling Hudson Bay", "correctAnswers": ["Canadian Shield"] },
            { "question": "Largest city of Wales", "correctAnswers": ["Cardiff"] },
            { "question": "Ecuadorian mountain whose peak is the farthest point from Earth's center", "correctAnswers": ["Chimborazo"] },
        ],
        'D': [
            { "question": "City with the tallest building in the world", "correctAnswers": ["Dubai"] },
            { "question": "Southernmost country in Scandinavia", "correctAnswers": ["Denmark"] },
            { "question": "Capital of the Emerald Isle", "correctAnswers": ["Dublin"] },
            { "question": "Country and capital in the Horn of Africa", "correctAnswers": ["Djibouti"] },
            { "question": "Largest city of South Africa's Garden Province", "correctAnswers": ["Durban"] },
        ],
        'E': [
            { "question": "Only African country with Spanish as its official language", "correctAnswers": ["Equatorial Guinea"] },
            { "question": "Country formerly known as Swaziland", "correctAnswers": ["Eswatini"] },
            { "question": "Mongolia's second largest city", "correctAnswers": ["Erdenet"] },
            { "question": "South African province home to Bhisho", "correctAnswers": ["Eastern Cape"] },
        ],
        'F': [
            { "question": "Largest city in the interior region of Alaska", "correctAnswers": ["Fairbanks"] },
            { "question": "Scandinavia's \"Land of a Thousand Lakes\"", "correctAnswers": ["Finland"] },
            { "question": "Historic renaissance city in Italy", "correctAnswers": ["Florence"] },
            { "question": "Southern Japanese city of 1.6 million", "correctAnswers": ["Fukuoka"] },
        ],
        'G': [
            { "question": "Port city in Scotland's western lowlands", "correctAnswers": ["Glasgow"] },
            { "question": "African country whose capital is Conakry", "correctAnswers": ["Guinea"] },
            { "question": "Country on the Caucasus Mountains", "correctAnswers": ["Georgia"] },
            { "question": "Region in northwest Spain home to Lugo and Vigo", "correctAnswers": ["Galicia"] },
            { "question": "Cold desert in Mongolia and China", "correctAnswers": ["Gobi", "Gobi Desert"] },
        ],
        'H': [
            { "question": "U.S. state that Kauai is located in", "correctAnswers": ["Hawaii"] },
            { "question": "Country where Tegucigalpa is located in", "correctAnswers": ["Honduras"] },
            { "question": "Japan's north island", "correctAnswers": ["Hokkaido"] },
            { "question": "Seaside capital of Nova Scotia", "correctAnswers": ["Halifax"] },
            { "question": "Central European country home to the largest synagogue in Europe", "correctAnswers": ["Oman"] },
        ],
        'I': [
            { "question": "Spanish Island known for its nightlife and EDM", "correctAnswers": ["Ibiza"] },
            { "question": "Country home to the world's most populous island", "correctAnswers": ["Indonesia"] },
            { "question": "City on the southern tip of New Zealand", "correctAnswers": ["Invercargill"] },
            { "question": "Turkish city formerly known by the Greek name of Smyrna", "correctAnswers": ["Izmir"] },
            { "question": "Russian city and oblast near Lake Baikal", "correctAnswers": ["Irkutsk"] },
        ],
        'J': [
            { "question": "Saudi Arabian port city on the Red Sea", "correctAnswers": ["Jeddah"] },
            { "question": "Largest city in South Africa", "correctAnswers": ["Johannesburg"] },
            { "question": "Indian metropolis known as the Pink City", "correctAnswers": ["Jaipur"] },
            { "question": "Capital of the U.S.'s Last Frontier", "correctAnswers": ["Juneau"] },
        ],
        'K': [
            { "question": "Country in the Middle East that shares its name with its capital", "correctAnswers": ["Kuwait"] },
            { "question": "Pakistani city with over 20 million people", "correctAnswers": ["Karachi"] },
            { "question": "Peninsula in Russia's far east", "correctAnswers": ["Kamchatka", "Kamchatka Peninsula"] },
            { "question": "Capital of Malaysia", "correctAnswers": ["Kuala Lumpur"] },
            { "question": "City of over 4 million in northern Nigeria", "correctAnswers": ["Kano"] },
        ],
        'L': [
            { "question": "Country in Europe that shares its name with its capital", "correctAnswers": ["Luxembourg"] },
            { "question": "Country bordering Syria and Israel", "correctAnswers": ["Lebanon"] },
            { "question": "Second largest city and industrial hub of Papua New Guinea", "correctAnswers": ["Lae"] },
            { "question": "Country home to the former Barbary state of Benghazi", "correctAnswers": ["Libya"] },
            { "question": "Mining hub and second largest city in the DRC", "correctAnswers": ["Lubumbashi"] },
        ],
        'M': [
            { "question": "Country with the city of Marrakesh", "correctAnswers": ["Morocco"] },
            { "question": "Capital city of Nicaragua", "correctAnswers": ["Managua"] },
            { "question": "Largest research station in Antarctica, located on Ross Island", "correctAnswers": ["McMurdo Station", "McMurdo"] },
            { "question": "Microstate between Milan and Marseille", "correctAnswers": ["Monaco"] },
            { "question": "Major northwestern Russian city on the Barents Sea", "correctAnswers": ["Murmansk"] },
            { "question": "Capital of Liberia", "correctAnswers": ["Monrovia"] },
        ],
        'N': [
            { "question": "U.S. state where Madison Square Garden is located", "correctAnswers": ["New York"] },
            { "question": "Indian island with virtually no contact with the rest of the world", "correctAnswers": ["North Sentinel Island"] },
            { "question": "Largest city in Greenland", "correctAnswers": ["Nuuk"] },
            { "question": "Niger's capital", "correctAnswers": ["Niamey"] },
            { "question": "Country home to Skopje", "correctAnswers": ["North Macedonia"] },
        ],
        'O': [
            { "question": "Capital city in the midwest of America", "correctAnswers": ["Omaha"] },
            { "question": "Notable waterfront city in northern Finland", "correctAnswers": ["Oulu"] },
            { "question": "Country home to Muscat", "correctAnswers": ["Oman"] },
            { "question": "Canadian province with Thunder Bay and Sudbury", "correctAnswers": ["Ontario"] },
        ],
        'P': [
            { "question": "Europe's largest rice growing region located in Italy", "correctAnswers": ["Po Valley", "Po Plain"] },
            { "question": "Landlocked South American country", "correctAnswers": ["Paraguay"] },
            { "question": "Brazilian state home to Curitiba", "correctAnswers": ["Parana"] },
            { "question": "City of 250,000 in northern Portugal", "correctAnswers": ["Porto"] },
        ],
        'Q': [
            { "question": "City in South America with a population of 2.8 million", "correctAnswers": ["Quito"] },
            { "question": "Country in the Persian Gulf", "correctAnswers": ["Qatar"] },
            { "question": "Mexican state where Cancun is located", "correctAnswers": ["Quintana Roo"] },
        ],
        'R': [
            { "question": "African country bordering Uganda", "correctAnswers": ["Rwanda"] },
            { "question": "Baltic capital known for its medieval Old Town", "correctAnswers": ["Riga"] },
            { "question": "Sea separating the Middle East and Africa", "correctAnswers": ["Red Sea", "Red"] },
            { "question": "Smallest U.S. state", "correctAnswers": ["Rhode Island"] },
        ],
        'S': [
            { "question": "State in Australia with Alice Springs", "correctAnswers": ["South Australia"] },
            { "question": "South American country whose official language is Dutch", "correctAnswers": ["Suriname"] },
            { "question": "Italian island home to Palermo", "correctAnswers": ["Sicily", "Sicilia"] },
            { "question": "Yemeni island known for its unique dragon blood trees", "correctAnswers": ["Socotra", "Socotra Island"] },
            { "question": "Indonesia island with Makassar and Manado", "correctAnswers": ["Sulawesi"] },
            { "question": "Russia's largest republic, home to Yakutsk", "correctAnswers": ["Sakha", "Sakha Republic"] },
            { "question": "Norwegian archipelago home to Longyearbyen", "correctAnswers": ["Svalbard"] },
        ],
        'T': [
            { "question": "Australian state that Cradle Mountain is located in", "correctAnswers": ["Tasmania"] },
            { "question": "Chinese region home to Lhasa", "correctAnswers": ["Tibet"] },
            { "question": "Malian city which was historically an important economic and academic center", "correctAnswers": ["Timbuktu"] },
            { "question": "Tech research center of over 200,000 in Norway", "correctAnswers": ["Trondheim"] },
            { "question": "Greece's second largest city", "correctAnswers": ["Thessaloniki"] },
        ],
        'U': [
            { "question": "City in southern Argentina known as the gateway to Antarctica", "correctAnswers": ["Ushuaia"] },
            { "question": "The secondary capital of Sweden, historically", "correctAnswers": ["Uppsala"] },
            { "question": "South American country home to Salto and Punta del Este", "correctAnswers": ["Uruguay"] },
            { "question": "Country home to Kyiv and Lviv", "correctAnswers": ["Ukraine"] },
        ],
        'V': [
            { "question": "Largest city in British Columbia", "correctAnswers": ["Vancouver"] },
            { "question": "Fishing village in southern Iceland", "correctAnswers": ["Vik"] },
            { "question": "Seaside port and resort city on the Bulgarian coast", "correctAnswers": ["Varna"] },
            { "question": "Liechtenstein's capital", "correctAnswers": ["Vaduz"] },
            { "question": "Italian city with canals instead of roads", "correctAnswers": ["Venice"] },
        ],
        'W': [
            { "question": "Sits near the North Island's southernmost point in New Zealand", "correctAnswers": ["Wellington"] },
            { "question": "U.S. state known for its cheese and beer", "correctAnswers": ["Wisconsin"] },
            { "question": "Appalachia's \"Mountain State\"", "correctAnswers": ["West Virginia"] },
            { "question": "Australian state with Bunbury, Geraldton, and Port Hedland", "correctAnswers": ["Western Australia"] },
        ],
        'X': [
            { "question": "Largest city in the world starting with X", "correctAnswers": ["Xiamen"] },
            { "question": "Vast Chinese territory home to Urumqi and Turpan", "correctAnswers": ["Xinjiang"] },
            { "question": "Capital of Mexico's Veracruz", "correctAnswers": ["Xalapa"] },
        ],
        'Y': [
            { "question": "Merida is located in this Mexican region", "correctAnswers": ["Yucatan"] },
            { "question": "Canadian province with a potato variety named after it", "correctAnswers": ["Yukon"] },
            { "question": "Myanmar's largest city", "correctAnswers": ["Yangon"] },
            { "question": "Capital of Cameroon", "correctAnswers": ["Yaounde"] },
            { "question": "Siberian city home to the Mammoth Museum", "correctAnswers": ["Yakutsk"] },
        ],
        'Z': [
            { "question": "City on the Croatian coast in between Zagreb and Split", "correctAnswers": ["Zadar"] },
            { "question": "Archipelago off the coast of Tanzania", "correctAnswers": ["Zanzibar"] },
            { "question": "Country home to Harare and Bulawayo", "correctAnswers": ["Zimbabwe"] },
            { "question": "Dutch province whose \"New\" version is more famous", "correctAnswers": ["Zeeland", "Zealand"] },
        ]
    };
}